And I want you to also think about and
talk about how it all happens.
So for three different scenarios,
you have your contractual work that you
do,
your wet checks or startups or shutdowns,
whatever you do in your market.
And then you have maybe the stuff that
comes from extra work that maybe you did
an assessment and you did,
you had some repairs,
so you sent the customer a proposal and
they approved it.
Mhm.
And then the third type is an emergency
show.
You get a call, you got a mainline break,
and you're headed out there to fix it.
Mm.
Okay.
So I'd like to think about how you,
you know,
what you guys do to get all that started,
you know, how you schedule it,
what kind of documentation you have up
front.
And then how you use the workbook.
Um...
I guess the workbooks is mainly for the
first two scenarios,
Mhm.
the contractual stuff and the work orders
or the sales orders.
Yep.
And then what you specifically output to
that to maybe generate a proposal or hand
it off to somebody. So am I making sense?
Okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, uh, let's see, see,
you wanna look at a completed report?
Yep, and just, yeah,
talk through it with those things in mind.
Yeah.
Sure, sure. Let me pull one up here.
And maybe bite size first, you know,
like talk us through contractual work.
Yeah.
Service.
Burns.
Swift.
Alright.
Right-sized.
Okay.
All right,
let me see if I can share this with you
now.
that we can see your screen.
Alright, Greg.
And, OK, so...
So this is our PMI inspection form.
You just want what we do step by step.
Yep.
Okay, yeah,
so the tech's going to show up on site.
He's going to find the controller.
This form we fill out on a tablet that
the tech has.
In Excel.
Do you guys, do you have maps?
Typically we have a site map.
Quite often we have a zone map,
not always.
Okay. What kind of,
what form are those in?
Is it like a just print a PDF? Okay.
PDF.
Yeah,
it'll either be a PDF that we then print
out. Yeah, or...
If we, you know,
the thing with maps is it helps us in the
long run. You know,
it's a slowdown to go fast thing.
So it takes time to set it up and to
actually produce a good product,
which helps us in the long run.
But lately,
we've got a lot of small accounts that
we've been.
handed off.
And so we're a little behind on our
mapping.
But when we have the time and where we
can get it done,
if we don't have an existing map and it
feels worthwhile,
we'll give them an overhead satellite
photo printout.
and let them sketch it out.
And then they'll bring that back to us
Okay.
and we'll generate a proper map with,
you know, zone listed,
controller location, Backflow.
And then per zone,
we'll note the distribution.
Type and the plant material.
And what tool do you use to create those
formal maps?
Some people use PDF Pro.
I've done a lot of it in Google Slides.
OK,
so you just draw on the map with those.
Um...
Yeah,
I like to draw in something that is
editable so that you've got flexibility
and you know, one thing happens,
you don't have to go back later on. Wow,
that was a really loud sneeze.
Yeah.
Hang on a minute. Hey, hey bro,
I'm trying to do business here.
Like.
You try to spend OK.
I sneeze like that.
Yeah. Yeah,
so I like to keep the maps in soft copy
And...
and then generate PDFs for the clients.
And, you know, we'll print one out,
Okay.
stick it in the controller that will keep
a database that the tech can have on
their tablet. And so...
That's how that starts.
The tech gets to the controller. Okay,
And so, and this got initiated.
yeah, stop me,
stop me whenever you have questions.
So this got initiated from this is
contractual work.
So you're sending them out there to do an
eval or a wet check or something.
Yeah, you know,
whatever the cadence is under the
contract or a startup inspection for us,
you know, a new job start or, I mean,
Okay.
our goal is to hit everything 4 * a year.
some of the contracts.
We have one contract that specifies a
monthly inspection, which I'm like,
you're not going to approve that,
so I don't know why we're doing it,
but that's that. And then, yeah,
we get into this part here on the
controller information and we get started.
I guess if we're talking the full...
the full job process,
then the tech should be doing a take two
on the site and getting that out of the
way, you know, doing a safety check first,
doing a quick lap. And then, yeah,
we get into controller data here.
Do we have a harness for our remote?
Is there a map?
Water type is it? I mean,
it's not going to,
you guys can dig into this form,
it's not going to show up at this
resolution.
But what is our water type?
What is our Backflow spec? Built this,
you know,
all the different types of Backflow
devices you could have.
And then over here, address,
controller spec,
picking from most of the common models.
that we see,
serial number if that's available,
and then which model it is specifically.
Um, and where it is, and then per zone.
We want to go through, and it looks like,
I wonder if this is broken,
but we want to note what kind of plants
do we have,
what kind of distribution are we working
with within that zone,
and take a resistance reading at the
controller terminal to see if we have
wire issues or failing solenoids.
to be aware of off the bat before we go
and try to activate the station.
So we start at the controller,
get everything we can from the controller,
and then do a resistance check,
and that's kind of baseline.
Erb.
And then per station,
this is just going through.
Now what we don't put on here that,
you know,
this doesn't tell the whole story because
where we have, you know,
heads that need to be straightened,
not vertically, but hey, no running.
Sorry, guys. I don't know,
but there's no running, dude.
Yes.
Thank you, Tucker.
Yeah.
Code in Breanne.
My branch manager and my accounts
receivable person, for some reason,
are chasing each other around the office.
Anyways.
Yes.
Things like adjusting coverage,
we don't put on the report,
we're supposed to do that anyways,
unless we're just there to look and not
touch.
That would be in a non-contract situation.
If someone's just like,
tell me what everything looks like,
and then we won't do those adjustments,
but in general, we're at least...
you know,
turning risers to correct coverage or
adjusting rotors,
their radius and throw if we need to on
the spot.
The rest of what goes in the report is
things that are broken or leaking or at
least in this first section.
And I get a lot of questions from clients.
What's
what's high priority? And I'm like,
water on the ground is high priority.
Or water that's not coming out at all,
where you've got valve issues,
solenoid wires,
where your whole zone is going to die,
high priority.
So we go through and note those per zone.
And then our upgrades are
Anything else that we want to see,
you know, your boxes look bad,
your lids have been destroyed by the
mower, your zone needs to be extended,
your heads need to be changed out for
taller heads.
Things like that go in that bottom
section there.
And we've expanded this recently.
Does this one have decoder on it?
Where's my decoder?
Yeah.
Oh
I feel like I'm missing a row here.
Yeah, because, well, if it's not there,
we should add decoders at some point.
But the struggle with this sheet is to
keep it to 1 printable page.
And so that's why I try not to just jam a
bunch of lines in it.
So, yeah.
But that's it.
They'll go through and they'll fill this
thing out for, you know,
note all the zones,
give us an home reading,
and give us the broken distribution.
And now these days,
A lot of clients are asking for...
pictures of the broken stuff that we're
noting on the report and they also want a
location of each broken sprinkler and or
drip cut and or lateral break on a map
which
is a pain and should make approval easier.
I don't see it happening yet, but perhaps,
perhaps it will do that for us in the
long term.
Yeah, that's it.
Tell me what questions you have.
And do you reuse this? Like,
do you create one of these for a property
Yeah.
and then every time somebody goes out,
they have this same workbook and they are
able to see what happened in the past?
That's,
it doesn't always happen that way because
sometimes the tech has, you know,
I have a master sheet,
they can make a copy of it and they'll
start fresh,
but I try to encourage them to take the
one you already did and maybe the piece I
need to do is getting in there before
they go out and making them a fresh copy
that's just ready to fill in.
That's the same information,
but just with the totals blanked out.
because there's no reason to take the
time on the tablet to go back through and
note, you know, it should be,
you're just verifying plant type and
distribution.
You shouldn't have to fill that out again.
That's a little efficiency that we could
gain, certainly.
And what's the result of this?
So after they finish this,
they note all of the call outs and things
that need to happen.
So funny.
Where does it go from there?
And is this the document that is the
Mhm.
So, from here...
output?
Yeah,
this document is the output and they'll
share it with me on a drive file.
So I can look at it. You know,
it lives on a,
we have a shared folder that this report
lives in.
And then I'll take it from there and
generate the extra work proposal and send
that to the client.
The client will get the extra work
proposal.
This inspection report, and...
Nowadays,
they're gonna get a photo gallery of the
brakes,
and they're going to get a location map
of the brakes as well.
So,
let's see if I have one I can show you.
Let me drag this up here.
And so you receive those things and
you're the one that creates the proposal?
Yeah, I do.
Or my lead tech has been doing a lot of
our proposal writing.
Let's see, I'm trying to see if I can,
if we've got all of our attachments in
here or if they're just in the email.
And
Yeah,
this one doesn't have any attachments.
So, quite often with this, I'll just do,
you know,
a one-line dollar amount that refers to
the report.
I've had clients that want to see every
line item.
as a line item on the proposal.
And I that to me is it's a bridge too far.
So I really try to fight that because I
don't agree with it.
And if we were to do that for everyone,
the amount of extra work that it creates
is a lot.
Because for our branch,
we're trying to propose,
we're trying to propose 300 and some
thousand a month.
Um...
So it gets to be a lot. Where am I?
Here we go.
So,
here's an inspection report we just did
Oh, nice.
Could you forward that one to me?
for.
Sure.
Yeah,
so here's what we just did for Oracle.
Come on, play nice.
Computer says you're trying to do too
many things.
So this is the report,
Oracle Controller A.
It's all pretty small for you to see
right here.
That's fine.
Okay. But you know, pretty standard.
So one thing this client recently they
asked us,
because we were having trouble with our
approval cycle,
everything was taking just a really long
time. They're managed by JLL right now.
And they asked us to break things down
under $2,500 chunks.
So that they could approve it,
because they have, you know, just...
they can sign on 2499 a lot faster than
they can on 10,000. So like this report,
we took it, it's $4,400,
and I talked to the client and said, okay,
I've got the report for the one
controller.
Can I send you 2 proposals and just give
you the same report with the
I.
understanding that we are playing the
game with each other here?
and would save us the labor of having to
split the report into two reports.
And they agreed to them.
So it would be an awesome feature to do
if you have 4 clocks on a property to be
able to generate a report just for one of
those clocks.
Be able to split the split a SO that way.
Sure, I mean, we have, yeah, for us,
this thing was the dollar amount,
Okay.
so we do,
we're doing one report per controller,
but...
But we're doing 2 SOs when we go over
that $2,500 threshold.
Right.
I'm trying to see inspection,
is the SO and where's our... Yeah,
see like this one, controller H,
we've got SO that ends in 899,
and then controller H,
we also have one that ends in 895.
Erb.
I was trying to see if we had repair maps
here or if the...
It looks like these are just...
the sheets,
but I know that we've collected the
photos that go with each report and like.
So, yeah, if you could,
if you could look for one like that that
Yeah.
has a mixture and maybe even a map.
Mhm.
like one formal maps and forward that to
us. I would appreciate it.
Now you are you talking about a map with
the repairs on it or just a zone map?
No, no,
just a just a like a as-built or whatever
the map built, yeah.
Okay, yeah, sure, that's fine. I mean,
I'll give you just an idea here.
What's a good one that we have?
So, here's what we did for Oracle,
just to say,
just because their campus is so big and
they have so many controllers.
to help them interpret the reports.
They were having a lot of questions of
Yeah.
like, well,
where exactly does this one water and
that one water,
which I totally understand,
especially once you look at the map.
But we made this for them to say, okay,
when you're looking at the report for
controller A,
here is where you're going to see those
effects, right?
Gotcha.
You're worried about trees.
You got a lot of trees here.
And so then when you look at that report
and you see there's a valve that waters a
tree zone and it's broken,
don't delay on your approval because
you're going to dry out all these trees.
So that, that was, that's that. But then.
See, what's this one look like?
One of the things we get is, you know,
more than one person making maps, so...
The levels of quality are not uniform.
This still works in the field.
This still helps the tech understand
where he should be looking when he pops
his own and to learn the site,
but it's not as detailed as some of our
other stuff.
Yep.
And I can send you, you know,
both of these.
As well as some other ones, this is the...
These are as builds. Oh, here we go.
This is a good one.
OK.
Yep, awesome.
Yeah, yep.
Yeah.
Okay.
Zone boundaries, et cetera.
Okay.
So I can send you examples of all this
stuff.
And...
And then back on the form.
And then...
Yeah.
What, I mean, what's the minimum required?
Yeah.
To complete this, I...
Minimum what?
Like,
are you are you asking them for the
Backflow spec and the water type every
time they?
Do you require them to have?
No, I mean,
that's that that's up that's up to that's
up to you as a manager.
If it's if it's trouble for the tech,
Okay.
I mean,
the thing I like about asking for that
information, water type should be obvious.
If they're on a recycled water site,
they should know it.
There should be signs everywhere.
Backflow spec both helps you understand
where it is if you don't know.
And if you need that information,
something comes up and the client goes,
oh,
I have a leaking Backflow and you don't
know,
you can go refer back to one of those
reports and then say, oh,
it's a 2 inch 825Y and probably either
get something set up for testing or.
or service, what have you.
But it's just more information is better,
always. That's my theory.
Really.
And I see that you have the pricing on
here. I'm sorry, Jay,
Hey, Alex.
were you going to say something?
Yes.
Oh no, I may have missed it earlier,
but if there's like a controller B&C,
Yeah
Yes.
Uh-huh.
would you just,
would you copy this page over and do a
Okay.
controller, or how would you do?
Yeah,
so I have different sheets where it has,
you know, all the way to F. And then what,
yeah,
you just copy them and then you just
relink all these cells and everything
Oh, gotcha. Okay.
should be fine.
I like to refresh it every once in a
Gotcha.
while because I'll make a master and then
I'll go back and look at it and someone's
broken a link or, you know,
something got deleted.
Yeah.
Right.
Yeah,
you want to check on that stuff always.
It's easy to fall into just feeling like
the sheet's doing the math,
but then you look up here and someone
changed a price or it's not calculating
anymore.
So it's good to start with one that you
Yeah, OK.
know is working and then copy them out to
make your.
Your master.
Got it.
Are you doing that like every year?
Do you change these year cost prices?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
And where are the where are those prices
coming from?
Yeah,
like this pricing that we have on here,
I think we redid this spring of last year.
Okay,
and where is this unit cost price coming
from?
That's our looking at what materials are
costing us and estimating typical time
spent on some of these repairs.
Do you maintain an extra work catalog of
prices that match this?
No, no, I use this.
And are you the one that updates this?
Yes.
Okay.
All right.
What about, you know, something that is,
do you have like a other line?
But they go Lynn.
So, I mean, we have,
I'll have people put notes down here.
Yeah, that's kind of it.
I probably could add more space for
comments if they had it, but in truth...
A lot of it with our texts,
like it's just, it's just conversation.
A lot of them aren't big typers is the
way I'm going to put that.
And so when you're going through and
making like just fine-tuning coverage
adjustments and things like that,
you don't even know that kind of thing,
right?
No,
because it's not something we're going to
charge the client for.
This is just to tell the client, you know,
here's what's wrong with your system or
that you could improve or that you're
going to need to do soon.
Yeah.
Um, okay. Jay,
do you have any questions about this,
about the form?
No. Yeah, I mean, like you mentioned,
Alex,
the hardest thing is to keep people from
screwing it up, right?
So being able to protect those sheets,
that's what I always try and do. But no,
Mhm.
it looks like it works good.
And do you know if...
Are other branches, you know,
in your market utilizing this one,
or does everybody have their own?
After using this one,
I've given it to several people,
but there's been changes in management.
And I will say,
so you asked about other situations,
like this is a contract PMI form that we
use for that purpose.
I also have a work order form that I
created for my team.
to use. We did it primarily at Google.
They can use it at other places.
It doesn't have dollar amounts though.
I use this pricing on this sheet and then
I'll go through and just add up each one
of those manually.
Yeah, so it's a different version of this.
It's not as...
comprehensive.
There's still a lot of information,
but it's not this form.
I can share that one with you as well,
but it doesn't have the prices.
Like it doesn't total out to a dollar
amount. I'll basically count hours,
count parts,
and then do the total separately because
I got to give Google every month a work
log of everything we've done.
And so I use those because it doesn't,
you know,
you're going to send a guy out for a
broken lateral,
he's not going to bust out this
inspection for him. It doesn't make sense.
Seems like most of what you do is
paperwork, Alex.
It's a lot of paperwork.
Yeah.
But I mean, how do you track all? I mean,
are you doing this daily where the techs
come back and give you their reports and
you?
So the text,
so you mean like inspections and work
Oh.
orders or?
Yeah, yeah.
For the inspections,
for Google specifically,
actually for all of them,
everything goes into a shared folder,
a Drive folder. So they grab a work order,
they fix it, they finish it,
they put it in there, I review it,
I put it in my work log,
I mark it as done somewhere on the file
in the title so it's obvious.
And I move through them like that. Yeah,
inspection reports,
we grab them as they come in,
write the proposals,
send them to the client.
They all stay in that folder.
And then at a certain point, you know,
I'll clean it out or I'll move them to
somewhere where it's obvious they've been
processed, they're done.
But yeah, it's a lot. I mean,
our goal for the branches.
What is it? 1.6 million this year.
So it's a lot of generating proposals.
Okay, so, um...
For a specific extra work sales order
that's created, a tech,
you give that to the tech and they just
go out and fix those specific things.
Mhm.
Do they do another evaluation when they
go out to do that?
So in this instance, you know,
this is this one that we're looking at
for intuitive. Building 100,
we'll get a PO from the client.
We will print the report and the map for
the tech, hand it off to them.
They should have their time coding ready
to go.
and they go out and just go zone by zone.
Now,
and this is one thing that we stress to
the clients to try to encourage them to
approve things on schedule is what do you
do in the situation where you go out,
you had two broken 6 inch pop ups in zone
14 and others.
an extra one.
If it's one extra one and they approved a
Yeah.
6000, 8000, $10,000 report,
I'm giving them a free sprinkler.
It's not worth my time to go try to get
that $68.
Okay.
Do you ever do like a next not to exceed
addition or something like that? Okay.
Oh yeah, we'll do that. Yeah,
a lot of people only want to approve X
amount. If we're getting a lot of extras,
which typically we find that when there's
been, you know,
the approvals are taking two, three,
four months,
well now you're going to get more wear on
the system and more broken things.
So at that point, I'll tell the client,
You know,
we're going to find more stuff when we go
out.
Or a common one that we get is you have a
broken lateral on the report,
which means water's not getting down the
line. You repair the lateral,
water gets down the line and just reveals
either another lateral break or more
broken sprinklers that you couldn't see
before.
Now we've got to go back to the client
Yeah.
and say, look,
And I explain that whole situation to
them. Some of them get it.
Some of them treat you like you're the
car mechanic, telling them, oh, well,
the defraambulator is connected to the
discombobulator. It's going to have to,
Right.
you know, 3,000 more. But it's reality.
And if it really, you know,
Right.
push come to shove, I'll say,
let's meet on site.
We can go look at this and I can show you
what I'm talking about.
Um...
Yeah,
but those are things that we know to
expect.
And you only really have to educate the
clients about that,
hopefully once or maybe twice.
Nobody likes it,
but that is how the system works,
literally.
Okay, and how do you handle emergencies?
Emergencies, we have a,
we'll roll somebody out, you know,
anytime day or night.
The tech gets paid 3 hours.
Whether or not they work 3 hours,
that's our minimum charge.
We will charge the client that.
Typically we have an on-call tech and
Hopefully there's no access issues.
But after and then and then yeah,
I'll just follow up with the proposal to
the client just for that instance.
And when it's an emergency and they've
gotten the phone call,
Okay, sure.
they're usually pretty good about getting
us paid.
Okay.
Are you guys currently using field
service management for irrigation at all?
Are you using the service appointments?
No? Okay.
Now.
No.
Do you know who your field service
coordinator is?
I think it's Jay.
OK, it's not it's not Jay,
somebody at your branch.
No, I am your, I am your trainer.
Oh, oh, oh, then it's in the branch,
it's probably our new guy, Paco.
Yeah.
Taco.
Francisco, what is it, Frankie? Maldonado?
Yes. Yeah, Francisco Maldonado.
Yeah.
Yeah, we, I mean, yeah,
I don't know what all the names you call
them, but...
Yep,
Daniel was part of the initial training
too, but yeah, Daniel Rico.
Which, Daniel?
Oh, he's not gonna be the one.
But I, yeah,
I think Francisco has been doing the most
Yes.
work lately.
Yeah, yeah, I see,
I see him working in it, so...
Yeah.
All right, do you?
But I'm just gonna keep saying it's Jay
when anyone asks me.
Yeah.
Do you have any regulatory requirements
that you guys have? Like...
utility reporting or...
Any drought requirements or anything that
you have to report to a local?
Both. So for recycled water sites,
there's an annual inspection that's
required. It's called an ASIR,
an annual self-inspection report.
So that has to be done.
yearly. Typically, those are due anywhere.
The due dates vary,
but anywhere from April to the end of
July, those will come due.
That's actually something that I use to
push clients to repair things because
you're certifying that they don't have
any broken distribution. So you, you know.
Ohh.
So you should be honest when filling out
the form and get them to pay you to fix
their sprinklers.
Inspection, I mean, there's regulations,
certainly mostly to do with backflows,
Okay.
but we don't typically inspect or repair
backflows in-house. We sub that out.
OK.
So,
so you actually remove them and send it
to somebody or whatever?
Oh.
Yeah,
we just will call someone to do the
inspection and the repair.
Mostly because it's hard to get people
Okay.
certified,
get people who are capable of passing the
Backflow exam. And once they do,
they realize before too long that they
can make more money just doing that. So.
So is there a is there an annual
requirement on backflows in your area or
Yeah,
they have to be inspected every year as
is it?
well.
And does the customer get that
notification and then they call you or
Typically, yeah. No, no,
they'll get the notification.
are you handling that for them?
Any other?
Local restrictions, things. OK,
that's cool. What area are you in again?
That's kind of it.
Lynn.
Beard.
Yeah, temper.
Can you hear the planes leaving San Jose
Airport going over the office right now?
Okay.
All right,
do you guys use any smart controllers?
Oh yeah.
What platforms are you guys using?
We got Weather Track, we got Hunter,
we've got some Rainmaster Eagle.
We've got.
We got some rain birds in the mix.
Baseline. Yeah, baseline.
Got a few baselines. What's that?
Any weather, Matt?
Weathermatic.
I don't think, you know what,
we do have a shopping center.
I think we have two weathermatics in the
portfolio right now.
Do you do you guys use any portals for
any of these to?
Yeah, we're on, I mean, all of them.
We've got base manager accounts.
We've got not the weathermatics.
I don't think those are actually online,
but weather track I'm running right now.
What do I have on there?
A 250 controllers.
So yeah, just a little bit.
Do those do those do those systems also
have like flow meters at the Backflow,
The.
so you could identify breaks and things
like that?
Some of them do, yep.
Some of them we've got several,
Okay.
we've got a lot of systems that have flow,
what I'll call basic flow,
where single point flow.
And then we've got a few systems that are
running OptiFlow where you're...
I don't know how familiar you are,
but you're taking flow data and you're
sharing that between 5:00 to 6:00
different controllers.
So, OptiFlow, and what was the other one?
I mean,
the other one is just kind of standard
flow.
I could direct wire to the clock.
Yeah,
either direct wired or through a flow
link, but single POC, single controller.
S.
one water source,
one controller makes it easy to watch and
manage and whatever.
When you get into some of our more
complex systems,
A little bit of a brain breaker.
Okay, and who watches all of that?
Do you manage, monitor that stuff or?
Bing.
Talking. You're talking to them. I do.
The guys that I have,
so we only have like the only people that
have a standing PO with us where we're
there every day is Google through JLL.
So I have guys that are there all the
time.
And so they're constantly looking at the
alerts and reviewing everything.
Other than that,
it'll be as they pop up or as they happen
to visit the site and
Truth be told,
I get so many alerts every day that a lot
of them go,
like I have a folder just to keep my
email inbox from exploding.
So we're not watching it 24-7 like a call
center,
but we do get alerts and we do respond to
them.
And are you,
do you help out other branches or are you
Yeah.
just,
is this just your branch and you can help?
And.
Yeah.
I'm assigned to this branch.
I do favors for other branches. I,
you know,
when they need our help or they need
troubleshooting help or they've got a
problem they can't solve, if we have time,
we will go to there.
But our goals in this branch are...
Aggressive, I'll say.
Okay.
And alright, so.
Would you be willing to pilot an
irrigation solution at your branch?
Sure.
Okay.
Sure.
As long as you're ready for me to say the
reality of this is I can't fit it into
Okay.
the amount of time I have in the day,
I'll try anything. Especially if,
Yeah, I, yeah, we are.
you know,
if it helps us do what we're trying to do,
but better, I'm for it. We are.
Okay.
We are pretty stacked,
and from what I've seen.
I'm trying to be nice here.
For what I've seen of some other branches,
not all other branches,
more organization is needed,
more information is needed,
more standardization is needed.
All right.
The.
Well, let me give you a, let's see,
hang on one second.
Yeah.
So what we're doing next,
we did include you in a broader group of
about eight other irrigation
professionals across the nation for
BrightView that are going to be helping
us develop the end solution for this.
Um...
So the next call that you,
you've probably already been invited to
it, I think you have.
We set it up for next week.
Like.
You'll start seeing some of the
standardization recommendations we're
making and also what this is going to
look like initially.
in FSM and what it's going to look like
for a tech in the field.
So that's the next steps.
And then we'll just be asking for you to
help us when we get the solution ready to
help us validate it with those other guys.
And then to actually test it in our
environment.
And then after it gets through all the
tests and everything like that,
then actually trying it out on real world
situations in a pilot.
Cool.
Our current goal is to have this live for
pilot in July.
Okay, yeah,
there's nothing going on in July,
Okay.
so that's good.
Yeah, nothing going on, so yeah.
Yeah.
Well,
our hope is that this will make your life
easier.
It is going to involve you using service
Totally.
appointments and having your irrigation
technicians using the FSM mobile app.
So that might be the entry point for your
team into that.
But yep, so that,
do you have any questions?
Okay.
No, I'm curious to see what it looks like.
Yeah, I want to see.
I want to see what it looks like for sure.
Hey, Alec,
you mentioned that your techs use tablets.
Do they use tablets or iPads or both or
what are they using?
Mhm.
They all have Galaxy tablets.
Galaxy tablets, okay.
Yeah.
And...
Yeah, and they're not.
They're not Brightview devices that we
get like from IT.
We'll just buy a tablet so that we can
run our stuff.
Okay, yeah,
that was my next question was if it were
a Brightview issued thing. Okay.
Nope.
Well,
we're just out here trying to make money.
Any more questions?
I'm good.
How's you, Alex?
Erb.
I think I'm good for now.
Okay.
Well,
I'd really appreciate some of those maps
and the output and proposals and photos
and things if you can follow up with
Okay.
Oh yeah, I'll get you that.
those. And
Sure.
And if I have any questions on those,
I'll let you know. Otherwise,
I'll see you again.
Yeah.
Next week.
Next week. All right, sounds good.
Awesome. Thank you so much, Alex.
Thanks a lot, guys. Yep, take care.
Thanks, Alex.
Erb.